const greetingsDataset1 = {
    id: 'greetings-1',
    name: 'Japanese Greetings 1',
    questions: [
    {
      question: 'What does "hai" mean in English?',
      options: ["Yes", "No", "Maybe", "Hello"],
      correctAnswer: "Yes",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "iie" mean in English?',
      options: ["Yes", "No", "Maybe", "Hello"],
      correctAnswer: "No",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "konnichiwa" mean in English?',
      options: ["Yes", "No", "Maybe", "Hello"],
      correctAnswer: "Hello",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "ja ne" mean in English?',
      options: ["Yes", "No", "Goodbye", "Hello"],
      correctAnswer: "Goodbye",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "sumimasen" mean in English?',
      options: ["Yes", "No", "Excuse me", "Hello"],
      correctAnswer: "Excuse me",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "arigatou" mean in English?',
      options: ["Yes", "No", "Excuse me", "Thank you"],
      correctAnswer: "Thank you",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "gome nasai" mean in English?',
      options: ["Yes", "No", "Excuse me", "Sorry"],
      correctAnswer: "Sorry",
    },
    ],
  };
  
  const greetingsDataset2 = {
    id: 'greetings-2',
    name: 'Japanese Greetings 2',
    questions: [
    {
      question: 'What does "すみません" mean in English?',
      options: ["Yes", "No", "Excuse me", "Hello"],
      correctAnswer: "Excuse me",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "ごめんなさい" mean in English?',
      options: ["Yes", "No", "Excuse me", "Sorry"],
      correctAnswer: "Sorry",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "ありがとう" mean in English?',
      options: ["Yes", "No", "Excuse me", "Thank you"],
      correctAnswer: "Thank you",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "はい" mean in English?',
      options: ["Yes", "No", "Maybe", "Hello"],
      correctAnswer: "Yes",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "こんにちは" mean in English?',
      options: ["Yes", "No", "Maybe", "Hello"],
      correctAnswer: "Hello",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "じゃね" mean in Englisg?',
      options: ["Yes", "No", "Goodbye", "Hello"],
      correctAnswer: "Goodbye",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "いいえ" mean in English?',
      options: ["Yes", "No", "Maybe", "Hello"],
      correctAnswer: "No",
    },
  ],
  }
  
  const pronounsDataset1 = {
    id: 'pronouns-1',
    name: 'Japanese Pronouns 1',
    questions: [
    {
      question: 'What does "watashi" mean in English?',
      options: ["I", "You", "He", "She"],
      correctAnswer: "I",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "anata" mean in English?',
      options: ["I", "You", "He", "She"],
      correctAnswer: "You",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "kare" mean in English?',
      options: ["I", "You", "He", "She"],
      correctAnswer: "He",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "kanojo" mean in English?',
      options: ["I", "You", "He", "She"],
      correctAnswer: "She",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "boku" mean in English?',
      options: ["I", "You", "He", "She"],
      correctAnswer: "I",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "ore" mean in English?',
      options: ["I", "You", "He", "She"],
      correctAnswer: "I",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "wareware" mean in English?',
      options: ["I", "We", "He", "She"],
      correctAnswer: "We",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "sore" mean in English?',
      options: ["Them", "That", "He", "She"],
      correctAnswer: "That",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "karera" mean in English?',
      options: ["Them", "They", "He", "Him"],
      correctAnswer: "They",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "kore" mean in English?',
      options: ["Them", "This", "He", "She"],
      correctAnswer: "This",
    },
  ],
  };
  
  const pronounsDataset2 = {
    id: 'pronouns-2',
    name: 'Japanese Pronouns 2',
    questions: [
    {
      question: 'What does "かれ" mean in English?',
      options: ["I", "You", "He", "She"],
      correctAnswer: "He",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "それ" mean in English?',
      options: ["Them", "That", "He", "She"],
      correctAnswer: "That",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "かのじょ" mean in English?',
      options: ["I", "You", "He", "She"],
      correctAnswer: "She",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "ぼく" mean in English?',
      options: ["I", "You", "He", "She"],
      correctAnswer: "I",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "おれ" mean in English?',
      options: ["I", "You", "He", "She"],
      correctAnswer: "I",
    },
  
    {
      question: 'What does "これ" mean in English?',
      options: ["Them", "This", "He", "She"],
      correctAnswer: "This",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "あなた" mean in English?',
      options: ["I", "You", "He", "She"],
      correctAnswer: "You",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "わたし" mean in English?',
      options: ["I", "You", "He", "She"],
      correctAnswer: "I",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "われわれ" mean in English?',
      options: ["We", "You", "He", "She"],
      correctAnswer: "We",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "かれら" mean in English?',
      options: ["Them", "They", "He", "Him"],
      correctAnswer: "They",
    },
  ],
  };
  
  const numbersDataset1 = {
    id: 'numbers-1',
    name: 'Japanese Numbers 1',
    questions: [
    {
      question: 'What does "ni" mean in English?',
      options: ["One", "Two", "Three", "Four"],
      correctAnswer: "Two",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "yon" mean in English?',
      options: ["One", "Two", "Three", "Four"],
      correctAnswer: "Four",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "hachi" mean in English?',
      options: ["Five", "Six", "Seven", "Eight"],
      correctAnswer: "Eight",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "go" mean in English?',
      options: ["Five", "Six", "Seven", "Eight"],
      correctAnswer: "Five",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "san" mean in English?',
      options: ["One", "Two", "Three", "Four"],
      correctAnswer: "Three",
    },
  
    {
      question: 'What does "juu" mean in English?',
      options: ["Nine", "Ten", "Eleven", "Twelve"],
      correctAnswer: "Ten",
    },
  
    {
      question: 'What does "roku" mean in English?',
      options: ["Five", "Six", "Seven", "Eight"],
      correctAnswer: "Six",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "ichi" mean in English?',
      options: ["One", "Two", "Three", "Four"],
      correctAnswer: "One",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "nana" mean in English?',
      options: ["Five", "Six", "Seven", "Eight"],
      correctAnswer: "Seven",
    },
  
    {
      question: 'What does "kyuu" mean in English?',
      options: ["Nine", "Ten", "Eleven", "Twelve"],
      correctAnswer: "Nine",
    },
  ],
  };
  
  const numbersDataset2 = {
    id: 'numbers-2',
    name: 'Japanese Numbers 2',
    questions: [
    {
      question: 'What does "じゅう" mean in English?',
      options: ["Nine", "Ten", "Eleven", "Twelve"],
      correctAnswer: "Ten",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "いち" mean in English?',
      options: ["One", "Two", "Three", "Four"],
      correctAnswer: "One",
    },
  
    {
      question: 'What does "さん" mean in English?',
      options: ["One", "Two", "Three", "Four"],
      correctAnswer: "Three",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "ご" mean in English?',
      options: ["Five", "Six", "Seven", "Eight"],
      correctAnswer: "Five",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "ろく" mean in English?',
      options: ["Five", "Six", "Seven", "Eight"],
      correctAnswer: "Six",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "よん" mean in English?',
      options: ["One", "Two", "Three", "Four"],
      correctAnswer: "Four",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "に" mean in English?',
      options: ["One", "Two", "Three", "Four"],
      correctAnswer: "Two",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "はち" mean in English?',
      options: ["Five", "Six", "Seven", "Eight"],
      correctAnswer: "Eight",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "きゅう" mean in English?',
      options: ["Nine", "Ten", "Eleven", "Twelve"],
      correctAnswer: "Nine",
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "しち" mean in English?',
      options: ["Five", "Six", "Seven", "Eight"],
      correctAnswer: "Seven",
    },
  ],
  };
  
  export const allDataSets = {
    greetings: [greetingsDataset1, greetingsDataset2],
    pronouns: [pronounsDataset1, pronounsDataset2],
    numbers: [numbersDataset1, numbersDataset2],
  };
  